So, yesterday a lot happened on
PulseChain. We had PulseX, pretty much
PulseChain go down, but not really. Then
we had Richard Heart come out and call
everyone leeches for using blockchains
the way they work on it every single
other chain. And then we saw Pulse take
a massive pump all the way up 106%
off of one buy.
Which was immediately sold back in less
than 1 minute. Yeah. These are minute
candles, guys. All right, let's talk
about it. Before we get into that, let
me let you guys know what I've been
hearing about more and Fuel. So,
moretokens.com got an update, small
update. When someone would start a
stake, they would have to set a date.
You could only set your unlock date. You
couldn't just choose how many days. So,
now you can choose how many days. Um we
actually got some new stakes coming
yesterday. So, we're up to 33,000 more,
up from 31,000 more yesterday. More is
actually up a lot in the past couple of
days. It's up since Fuel's announced.
It's up about 161%
and it's holding up. We had somebody buy
some more this morning and staked it.
They staked it for 324 days. That's
pretty good, man. Pretty inspiring.
Also, we got some bleeding stakes. This
one's been lost for 116 days past due.
So, maybe go check if you staked on
more, go to moretokens.com, check your
stakes, um and see if they're past due.
You might want to claim those because if
you haven't, um they're bleeding. Also,
I was sent this screenshot of the white
paper, the self-funding marketing
engine, where you mint Fuel, you are now
paid to grow your global mints. You
promote new users to mint because every
user that mints after you gets you more
Fuel. If people mint after you, you get
more coins. Every mint pays a fee, a
starting claim fee. Every claim and
re-mint auto starts the mint. And this
all fuels a buy and burn. So,
essentially, when you start a mint in
this protocol, Fuel, you're pretty much
married to it because when you come back
to claim your rewards, it automatically
starts a new mint for you for you to
then come back again and claim again and
keeps repeating the cycle. So, we have
this flywheel that is always fueling
iron burn pretty much automatically. So,
I'm very excited about this. This is
going to be coming out hopefully by the
end of this month. Come to the telegram.
The white paper should be out next week.
Testnet will be followed after that.
We'll have a private testnet then a
public testnet and
get to the telegram and learn more. So,
yesterday a funny thing happened. I was
doing a video for my members. I'm not
trying to shill or anything. It's just
It just That's what I was doing. I did a
member video yesterday.
You know, click the member button if you
want to go watch it, but I went to use I
was trying to use actuator. It's
basically this thing where it you can
start a hex stake and then sell the hex
stake and then buy the hex back and just
keep doing that and just I don't know
starting stakes or something. I wanted
to test it out see what it was about and
it wasn't working. It wasn't loading or
anything and I'm like, man, this is
garbage.
Right? I kind of gave it a bad rep. I'm
like, what's going on with What's going
on with the pulse chain? So, I go to the
feed and I'm seeing all these
screenshots about downtime on pulse X.
And I'm like, oh, well, that's not pulse
X. That's the whole chain because
nothing is working. It's just that
there's nothing else to do on pulse
chain besides pulse X. Like Like let's
be real. What else can you do with this
is it PV doing? So, everybody just
thought pulse X was down. No, the chain
was down. Now, it wasn't down. It was
the RPC. So, when you go to Let's go to
my test wallet here. Add custom network.
So, every chain uses an RPC.
So, you go to chainlist, right? And type
in pulse chain. You get all these RPCs,
right? And all the RPCs basically
connect you to the network. Sometimes
there are bad ones that don't work,
right? So, apparently the main RPC for
pulse chain, the one that everyone is
using stopped working. So, what does
Richard Heart do? Say, you know what,
Guys, sorry about that. Had some issues,
dropped the ball. Um, here's how we can
help you can get around that next time
while we wait on an update uh
from the devs to fix the RPC. No, of
course not. He gaslights and blames his
community
for not running their own RPC, not
having the the knowledge to have their
own RPC set up, not using the main one
like they do for every other major
blockchain like Ethereum, which
never goes down. Can't remember a time
where I was like, man, Ethereum's not
working right now.
Never happened.
And then you guys were like, won't you
focus on more on PulseChain? Why? I
already built what I built on on
PulseChain, you know? And the more on
PulseChain, they're bonded. You know,
the prices are pretty much the same
because they're bonded through
liquidity. There's even an arbitrage
opportunity, right? You could buy more
on PulseChain right now, bridge it over
to ETH, and then sell it for 9 cents.
Like, so fuel on ETH, it's going to help
the more on PulseChain anyway. But, it's
this type of thing where it keeps me
from taking the chain seriously. Like,
especially if something happens and
you're going to say, Pro Chip, if you
don't run your own node, you are a leech
of those who do.
What?
What are you talking about? Like, some
of the stuff that I I
kind of still amazes me that a lot of
you guys are still fans of this guy,
man. Like, it was cool, it was funny at
first, but it's like, oh, you really
like that? Like, you're really
he's an abuser. And if you think about
it, look remember his setup, like, he
has the the setup of someone who likes
torturing people and tying them up.
And
how do you like that? You know, he's got
like a layer type like like setup in his
room. This dude has some type of he
there's something wrong with this [__]
man. Let's ask him real quick.
There's nothing wrong with him, okay?
You could still have said this, but
saying it, calling people a leech
because they're just using the public
node. Like everybody ain't trying to
hide from the feds, man.
You can just use the public RPC, man.
Everything ain't We're not trying to
hide, you know, like you.
You know? And he like projects that on
everybody like like everybody ain't
really tripping about privacy like that,
man. Like privacy is cool, yeah, sure.
But if you ain't got nothing to hide
why you trying to be so private?
So, yeah, basically gaslights the
community, says run your own node, kids,
and uh that was that. He later came back
and said that the devs updated the UI so
that you could select an RPC, putting
your custom RPC for those nerds who do
want to do that, who want to go the
extra mile, you know? Sure. He could
have did that. He could have said all
that. He could have said, "You know
what? Sorry about that, but just a
heads-up next time, add your own RPC.
Did you know that you can run your own
RPC? So, you don't have to worry about
that. Now you know." Well, that's kind
of passive-aggressive, too, but you
know, he could have been nicer about it,
and it would have got way more respect.
Richard Heart needs some kids, man. Like
that's what he needs. He needs some
kids. Like if he had kids, he would stop
being like this. You know, maybe he
don't need kids. He might be kind of
abusive to him. I don't know. But
uh hopefully he won't be like that with
his kids. And if he wasn't like that
with his kids, then maybe he'd stop
being like this online. I think he's
kind of like he wants somebody to He
wants to tell people what to do. If you
want to tell people what to do, you need
to get some kids, man. You tell them
what to do. And you love them at the
same time. It's pretty cool.
Um
and then he can probably, you know,
that'll start to mirror his online
presence. And then we got this massive,
you know, I say we when I'm talking
about PulseChain, but it's like I'm not
really
>> kind of into it, but I see that's what
y'all are into the most. So, it's like,
oh, let's just talk about that. There
was this massive candle on pulse. It
pumped over 100% and it was immediately
sold down. Now, people were speculating.
Let's read some of the speculations.
Here's pulse scanner. I've been going
over some wild transactions on pulse
chain today. Theory one, some sort of
market manipulation that went horribly
wrong. The setup, bridging around
$250,000
worth of wrapped BTC you I mean
e-wrapped see like come on guys. This
type of I'm trying to help pulse chain
cuz I got some, you know, but this
e-wbtc,
yo, y'all are not the main chain, man.
>> [laughter]
>> Pulse chain is not the main. Just say
wrapped BTC cuz then you start confusing
people. E-wbtc,
man, it's the real b-wbtc, man. So,
$250,000 worth of
wrapped Bitcoin, die and eat. Phase one,
dump stable coins ETH for 27 billion
pulse. And he uses the pulse to buy
wrapped Bitcoin. Transaction goes
through. Transaction reverts. So, I
don't know why he would do it like that.
Who What What was the point of that?
What were you trying to get? You know,
I'm I'm really curious about what they
were trying to do. But, whatever they
were trying to do didn't work. So, you
can see when they bought, immediately
after arbitrage bots. So, what what what
could have went better with this is they
would have should have done smaller buys
and they would have gotten a way cheaper
price. But, because they did one massive
buy like this, they pumped the price,
which is actually kind of bullish.
Hear me out.
This is kind of bullish, man, because
this buy,
relatively speaking, was kind of a small
buy. It wasn't small, but you could
would done that on any any other
blockchain you do that any major
blockchain you do that doesn't pump the
price that much the price pumped 100%
off of that one buy of 136,000.
That's a lot, but if you would have
asked me without giving me the numbers
of pulse chain without me knowing how
much liquidity is in pulse in the the
pulse x pair stuff like that, you know,
I would have I wouldn't have thought
that the price would pump 100% off
136,000 liquidity. I would have probably
guessed like 10 20 because I still have
the old numbers in my mind, but seeing
it pump that much off 136k. It's
actually kind of bullish because that
means it doesn't take much to move the
price. You know, at this point get 700k
in liquidities is kind of thin. So
liquidity is getting thin on these
[clears throat]
pulse chain coins and we see the
liquidity on hex pulse chain is 300k. So
the liquidity on chain is actually
pretty low and it's could be lower, you
know, not it's not send it low, but I
mean 100 and that was that felt like a
that felt like Richard Heart guys. I'm
not going to lie from being around hex
the beginning
that felt like a Richard Heart candle.
That was just hard back down,
but he's
I don't want to keep putting him on this
pedestal, but there's no way he didn't
walk away from hex with a whole a
gigantic stack of eth and just all the
stuff that like
I talked junk about Richard Heart, but
then I remember why I was a fan like
yeah, this dude was early on and a lot
of the stuff they say about him having
um
being an early early investor in eth, I
believe that stuff. I think and you look
at hex, he pumped hex because the
liquidity was low. I talked about this
in the last video.
But he pumped hex because the liquidity
was low. He was able to pump hex because
the liquidity was low. And it's kind of
like what I said yesterday is is he's
waiting for it to get light. It's the
same thing with more like it's a very
light coin for me. Not to say that I'm
going to pump it, but but when people
buy when anyone buys it goes up a lot.
It's up 100% in a week and probably any
participation is like a couple guys just
seeing the vision. So PulseX liquidity
is at a million actually, which is
interesting. It's kind of large. It
pumped also. So, yeah, it's kind of
bullish. It's telling me PulseChain is
kind of light and it could get lifted,
but it would only work PulseChain will
only go well if Richard Heart is the one
behind pumping it. Anything else this
whole community thing, y'all are just
playing pretend, man. Like it's all
pretend that y'all you guys
marketing sucks, you know? It's not
good. Your your marketing you need
somebody from the outside to come in and
like PulseChain.
You need people you need normies. You
ever notice how like all the other
chains seem so much cooler like Solana,
Robinhood, base like it seems cool over
there, doesn't it? And that's there's a
reason why. I can't quite put my finger
on it, but I think it's just the the way
the people talk on Twitter put a vibe
out there and it seems cool and that's
where you should be. PulseChain doesn't
have that and
I don't know how you can get it. My
guess is all you older guys get some
cartoon PFP's.
Stop
cuz
>> [laughter]
>> cuz it's just like it's kind of cringe,
you know? Even me I'm about to mean my
old my picture is still kind of old. Not
not that old, but you got if you got a
lot of gray hair, it's time to pack it
up, man. It's time to pack it up.
Make a cartoon character of yourself
and say silly stuff. Yeah, I only
believe in PulseChain is if is if
Richard Heart is going to pump it. And
that's kind of it's always kind of been
like that because it's just not a it's
not a very cool community. It's not a
community that it screams, "I want to be
in that." It's not it. With Robinhood
it's like that. Solana is like that,
too. But all it takes is, you know, this
just chart pumping
and then going again like today. I
wouldn't be surprised, bro. I really
wouldn't if it pumps again today. If it
happens, maybe [clears throat] not
today, but like somebody's Here's the
bullish case. You guys want a bullish
case? I got one. It's It's forming a
bottom right now. Like if I would Who
Who got 136K
to throw away like that in one candle?
I don't think many people would. If you
got 136,000
dollars, you ain't yoloing a candle like
that.
It If If you don't have millions
[clears throat]
more somewhere else. You get what I'm
saying? Like
136K is a lot for somebody to use to buy
a coin, especially in this market. So if
you got 136K
or 250 or however much it was, you can't
be but so stupid anyway. Cuz how did you
get the money? So you got to be kind of
smart and kind of savvy. And I think the
fact of the matter is I think Richard
Heart is turning a I think the bullish
the bullish case is it's turning around
now. He's about to start pumping it.
But I don't know. I I don't I wouldn't
buy. I'm not buying off of that. But I
would not be surprised if like right now
it starts just like reversing and going
up because that was a Richard Heart S
candle. Um maybe it wasn't.
[clears throat] Let me know in the
comments how wrong I am cuz, you know, I
don't really I'm not really looking into
it. Oh, here's the transaction right
here. We I dug into it. Look, I don't
care that much, man. I just seen them
right here. I mean, I didn't click I
didn't I didn't click into it and see
cuz I don't care that much.
So, y'all let me know.
But, I wouldn't be surprised if that was
Richard Heart and he's
testing it. And I mean, the funny thing
about our those bots or who or whatever,
they can't sell forever. So, the only
way this thing goes up is if Richard
Heart pumps it. And I think he knows
that. So,
um the fact that they're still That's
good. I had just called him out for not
for not tweeting about PulseChain. They
fixed the uh UI that shows some RPC
stuff. That's good. But, anyway, go to
moretokens.com, stake some more, look at
the stats, get ready for fuel. Links to
everything around in the description if
they're not in the comment section. And
I will talk to you guys in the next one.
Peace.